Hello Hello friends, whenever we buy
any medical insurance policy for any action, the
first question we ask is
whether this zero decoration can be
added to our insurance policy
because we know its benefits
because it has a lot of benefits in it
that if a claim ever comes and there is
no problem with our vehicle, then
whatever part of yours is replaced or repaired,
you will get its full MRP, no
depreciation will be
deducted from you, but if your vehicle is more than five-six years
old or you have deliberately
not taken protection cover, then
how much part will you get,
this information about different parts becomes important for
you to know, if ever a claim comes then
you should know how much claim you should
get, Hello friends, my name is
Harvinder Singh and you are welcome
to the YouTube channel of DSE Solutions, friends, if
you want to know very good information related to insurance
and if you feel
that you may need it in future, then
please subscribe to the channel, it will be
beneficial for you that you get this  It will be
very easy to access the video and you and I will remain
in touch and I will also know
what information my viewers
want to know but top want to watch this video
so friends let's start
this video and watch this video till the end
then I promise you
that your details will become absolutely
clear that how much money you are going to get from which partner
if your policy is
not zero decoration then first of all let's
talk about major categories
in which categories all these cards are divided according to the depression there are
four major categories first of all it
is plastic end
part plastic orpat as it is clear from the name itself
that all the plastic
parts are front bumper rear bumper
side morning safe and to be more precise which is made
of plastic along with drop and like
your tyre-tube and along with it battery in between there is
a load in this category
this second dip is 50% 50% means
if your claim form the cost of the part is
part MRP which  If it is worth thousand rupees
then insurance companies will
not give ₹500 as clean and you will have to pay ₹500
from your pocket and how about the tyre, let
me tell you one more thing that if the damage is
on the empty tyre then insurance will
not give you coverage for it, for that
you will have to take tyre secure cover separately,
if the entire vehicle is involved in an accident along with it, only then
you will not get one.
Now the second category comes under this, there are
party inquisitives against glass parts about you, in
which a friend's installation came,
which is the front part, the rear part, the
side part, all these are
in glass pot and one special thing in this is that no
one will take advantage of you,
you will get the full price only if the MRP is of the party,
why is this so, see, the
special quality of the glass is that as long as the tyre
is complete it is not hidden, there is no
depression in it, there is no side of it, I cannot tell
what has happened, if it breaks then
its value is lost, it is completely lost, that is why the
parts  But there will be
no depression charge in your vehicle, you will get the full MRP
of the part, your
vehicle insurance policy is zero depression,
this is a simple normal comprehensive policy,
now it is the turn of friends, the third category is
fiber glass parts, these are very few,
fiber glass parts inside the vehicle means
that some components are made in the vehicle by mixing some parts of plastic and glass,
like your typing balance or
pan balance or even some part of the bumper, so the
rate of depression in those parts is thirty percent, that is, if there is a
part of thousand rupees, then
you will get 700 rupees out of that, ₹300 calculation means the
cost of depression i.e. incompleteness will be charged and
in normal, you will get 70% claim to and thirty
percent application will be deducted, friends, now
comes the turn of the final category, that is
metal parts, whether aluminum or metal,
whatever
five parts are made of metal, like the bonnet of your body, the
rear, all the four doors, this is
something of mutton  Whether it is an engine part or
any other thing, how much application will be required in it,
but friends, it is decided according to the age of the vehicle
and its rear part, you can
see it given on the screen, if
your vehicle is less than six months old, then there will be
no depression in it,
you will get the full MRP of the vehicle only, if it is a
very hard earned car from six months to one year, then there will be a
five percent deduction, if it is 1 to 2 years old then 10
percent, if two to three years 15 percent,
three to four years 25 percent, if 4 to 5 years 35 percent
and if the vehicle is 5 to 10 years old then it will be 40 percent
and if it is more than 10 years
old then there is a full 50 percent, the
deduction will go up to 50%, so you can
calculate that percentage at the time of your claim, you
can watch the video, if you need it, then
continuously subscribe to the channel, it will be
very useful for you whenever you
need it, so friends, I hope
that now you have understood this entire topic,
I will make you do a little
scarcity once again  Yes, there are 4 categories in this, the
first one is your plastic and fiber,
which is of tree snake, in which your
face has become a plastic part, along with the
tire-tube and your battery, so
your application in this is fifty
percent part, fiber is
thirty percent inside the glass and the glass, that is, the
head, because the glass parts are there, there is
no one and a half in it, you will
get the medal according to the whole, your parts are according to a calculation,
I have stitched it, now I have shown it to you in the video and
I have also told you about it, if you
want you can also take a screenshot of it, let's
see it in the video, so
friends, I hope you
liked the information a lot and if you
liked the video, then please like this video
and do not forget to share it, so friends,
with the hope that you remain healthy and happy, we will meet you
in the next video
with more good information and updates, till then
Namaskar A
[Music]
is done